Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you!
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, and so elusive?
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me!
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you!
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see!
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in wonder!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary lives.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in one another.
Rumble Ball
The effect of the rumble
ball lasts three minutes.
All the time I need to take you down.
Three minutes?
You couldn't defeat me in three
years, let alone three minutes.
Just three? Amazing.
Just three?
No way.
Well, all right.
This should be an interesting battle.
Come on, you old bat.
Let me up so I can help. Rumble!
You're no match!
Not against this!
Marimon Snow Melting Arrow!
Lock point! Light boost!
Huh, just a transformation, eh?
I was expecting something more.
All you have to show
are Devil Fruit powers.
You're a zone type, just like Dalton.
So, you're a reindeer human, huh?
Heavy point!
Wait, wait, boost.
No, I'm a human reindeer.
Same thing,
and I know everything
there is to know about
the three form transformations
you sometimes use.
Marimo's big super
surprise Katorea hammer.
Speaking of surprises, you've
got none left to spring on me.
I've seen all your forms now.
You're nothing more than a
power fighter like Dalton.
So there's no way you can.
Jumping point, jump, boost.
Get the jump on me!
Jeez, that guy can really jump. Whoa!
What the?
I don't get it.
What is that form?
Wasn't this human and animal form
the little reindeer from earlier?
What now?
Guard point, they're boost!
Another form?
No way!
I hit you dead on!
It won't work!
How is this possible?
You zone types have a three-form limit!
What the heck are you?
The Rumble Ball is a
special pill that enhances
the power of the Devil
Fruit's transformations.
Over five long years of research,
I discovered four additional
transformation points.
A-a seven-form transformation?!
That's impossible!
I don't believe it!
A talking reindeer who can
change into seven forms?!
Your friend, what's the matter with him?
There's just so much happiness of meeting
a transforming reindeer a guy can take!
You bastard!
Did you forget about fighting me?!
I won't be deceived by what
has to be an obvious sham!
It's not one!
Arm point, arm boost!
If you thought that was something,
you should see what my iron
hose can do against rocks.
Not my hammers! What nerf!
These'll teach you...
Barmo's Super Surprise Katorea Axe!
Snow-Splitting Flame!
Wow, damn, that reindeer
can really take a hit.
Damn, you dodged it!
Let's see you dodge! Yes!
I'm the directional soul splitter!
You're gonna take me down, huh?
You're not fighting, you're just dosing!
Brain point, brain boost!
I wasn't just dodging your swings.
I was looking for your weak spot. What?
This'll finish you. Skull!
A beam!
He's gonna shoot a beam!
No he won't, you idiot!
Hey, you shut your trap!
I'm telling you, it's gotta be a beam!
How do you know that, huh, Mr.
Smart Guy?
I just do!
Fine, what kind of beam?
A ginormous beam!
The castle's unguarded.
Looking for my weak spot, huh?
Well, I've got some news for you!
I don't have one!
Your little transforming parlor
tricks can't save you now!
And as you're about to find out,
you're the one who's gonna be finished!
Found it!
His jaw!
Where'd he go?
A friend?
Race!
Three minutes.
Yeah! All right! Wow! Hey, Luffy.
Yeah? Where is he? Where's who?
That tin-plated bastard, he's not here!
Well since his hippo got knocked away, I
doubt he could have snuck off very far.
Yeah, but how? When'd he go?
Probably when you were drooling
over those transformations!
How sneaky!
I'll find him!
Where do you think he ran off to?
There's not much up here, just the castle.
And Nami's all alone in there!
If he lays a finger on her, I'll chop
him up and feed him to the sharks!
Hold it!
Oh, well.
I guess the nincompoop has a death wish.
What?
I go away and this is what happens?
Drunk Castle used to be a stately palace!
Now it's nothing but a run-down
hobble filled with snow!
What did they do to it?
Oh, I won't let them get away with this.
I'll chew them up until there's
absolutely nothing left!
We've gotta get Vivi home.
I've spent enough time resting.
Doctorine doesn't seem to be around, so
maybe I can slip away without her noticing.
Great.
Looks like the coast is clear.
What? What the? Who's he?
Well, well, another Straw Hat, I presume.
Uh-oh, he doesn't look friendly.
Huh?
Straw Hat?
What's that mean?
I'm sorry, sir, but I don't
know what you're talking about.
What?
Oh, I was wrong?
Yes, I'm just a traveler who is passing
through, and I'm actually on my way out.
Oh, I see.
Nice talking to you.
See ya. Right.
Liar!
The king of this country
commands you to starve!
No, I won't!
Get away from me, you big creep!
I must have gained weight recently.
Well, I can fix that.
Much, much, factory!
Uh, what is he?
He turned into a bucket?
Ah, my miraculous bone structure
shaping technique is now complete!
I'm leanin' mean!
I'm hungry.
Time to gobble you up, Straw Hat. Ah!
Found you! Huh?
Hey, that's funny.
Wasn't that guy Big Fatso before?
So,
do you mind telling me
why the coat I kindly
loaned you is all torn
up before I murder you?
Do you have any idea how
much I paid for that thing?
28,800 berries!
That was after hackling!
Hey, wait, I didn't do it!
That loudmouth over there did!
It's not my fault he shot a cannon at me!
Okay, then in that case, Luffy,
I guess I can forgive you.
To be honest,
I should have known that
you would have never brought
it back in good condition
when I let you borrow it.
You can just pay me back at my usual 300
% interest, which comes to 100,000. Ah!
You should have said!
I would never have taken it then!
Hello!
I'm still here!
Oh, that's right, I still
gotta kick your butt!
Ha!
I'll be the one doing the butt-kicking!
Behind me lies this castle's arsenal, and
I'm the only one who has the key to it!
Inside its walls are some of the
most fearsome weapons known to man!
All I need to do is
devour them Straw Hats!
Then my munch-munch shock will
make them part of my body!
and you'll be forced to
face a fearsome living
weapon the likes of
which you've never seen!
The two of you don't stand a chance!
I hope you're ready to die, Straw
Hats, because I'm going... Hey.
Huh?
This isn't over!
Hey, he's getting away! Come back!
At least I've got another trump card!
This must be the key to the
arsenal he was yapping about.
Geez, why couldn't it have been the
key to this castle's treasure vault?
Oh, man.
Nami, my love!
Thank heavens!
I'm glad you're safe!
Sanji, what happened?
Why are you crawling?
Are you okay?
I'm great now that I've
seen you, Nami dear,
but there are two things that'll
make me feel even better.
If I could just rest my
head on your warm billowy.
No way!
Ready, please?
Run all you want!
You can't get away from
me, you stupid loudmouth!
The upper levels are full of snow, too?
Trash my castle and defy
my orders, will they?
They won't get away with this.
It's time I taught those in
support, and it's a lesson!
A painful lesson!
To do so, I'll use the ultimate
weapon of the entire Trump Kingdom!
My devastatingly lethal.
Tin Titan Royal Crown?
Seven Barrel Cannon!
Oh yeah?
Well, I've got you cornered!
On the contrary, Rubberman!
Time to die!
Snowbird's cool!
Stop it!
How dare you laugh at me! Shut up!
Dr. Ean. Hmm?
That guy.
Did you hear him?
He called me his friend.
I have to admit I was skeptical when I
heard about this ropeway to the castle.
But here it is, just like
the young man told us.
This place looks familiar.
Didn't it used to be Dr.
Correa's house?
Great view from this thing, huh?
Yeah, but isn't it just the
teensiest bit overcrowded?
We can't let Dalton go
alone when he's injured.
We'll fight alongside him.
Okay, I get it.
But we're so overloaded, it'll
take forever to get there.
You!
You gotta pedal faster!
Dalton, please just relax.
Wapol, who do you think you are, Dalton?
There's no medicine that
can cure fools, you say?
Did you call me the king a fool?
What, do you think you're some hero who
speaks for the lowly subjects of my kingdom?
Don't make me laugh!
You're just a servant!
A week in this cell will give you plenty
of time to reflect on your mistake.
There's nothing like prison
to change a man's attitude.
And just in case that doesn't work,
I'm going to have that rebellious
streak beaten out of you!
You're an excellent
god the citizens trust.
Don't be a fool.
Apologize to the king and
show him respect, Dalton.
That dead Dr.
Hiriluk was an idiot.
I can't believe you fell for his nonsense.
Risking your status
and insulting the king?
Have you lost your mind, Dalton?
I'll grant you a full pardon, Dalton.
All you have to do is get on your
knees and say they're following.
I'm so sorry, oh great King Wiper.
You always know what's
right for this country!
To hell with status!
To hell with the king!
You dare mock me too, stupid bird!
I'm the king of drum!
Yeah, so what?
It doesn't matter if you're a
king, or even if you're a god!
It doesn't matter if you're someone who's
great or someone who's not so great.
I'm still gonna kick your lousy butt.
It does matter, Straw Hat.
Trump Kingdom is a member
of the world government.
Don't you know what that means?
It means this is a capital
offense because I'm the king!
Like I said, Big Mouth, it doesn't matter.
King or no king, I'm taking you down.
Oh, really?
Well, not if I...
Take you down first, Strowhand!
That won't work.
But this will much,
much shock Tang Cannon!
Ah, his tongue turned
into a cannon! Goodbye!
Dalton!
Someone help me lift him!
Dalton, can you hear me? Dalton!
I'm okay.
Please don't die!
I won't.
I can't.
Not until I put an end to Wobble
and what he's done to this country!
A government should care about
its country and its people.
You mean you weren't joking?
That's what you really think, Dalton?
Please, a government doesn't
need to have a heart.
That's right.
It just needs to control the people.
What are you doing? Unhand me!
Stop it! Let me go!
You can't do this!
I have patients who will
die if I don't treat them!
Throw him in the ocean!
If he resists, you have my
permission to shoot him!
No!
Think of my patients at least!
They're the ones who are going to suffer!
Don't do this!
To hell with controlling the country!
God.
And none of them are sick.
Show them what happens to a
country that doesn't have a heart!
dynamite.
everyone listen!
once we arrive.
take cover.
because once I'm inside.
there'll be explosions.
that idiot!
he let his guard down.
pollock is talking. Huh?
One, two...
Hey, what are you doing?
That!
No, stop!
Go, go!
Go, go, go!
Dr.
Rain, it certainly seems
like it's finally over.
I told you not to mess with that flag.
Now I'm sorry.
I'm finally going to kick your butt!
Doctor...
Wait a minute!
I'll give you a battle of the position!
Look, there's something going
on on top of the castle!
Doctor...
This...
This kingdom...
Drum Kingdom, it's...
Fine!
I'll make you vice king!
It's about to fall!
Bazooka!
So the Drum Kingdom was ultimately
defeated by the Skull and Crossbones.
Everybody, wait here.
I'll brave whatever dangers lie ahead
and let you know when it's safe.
I'm going first.
Hey, what the hell are you doing?
Just watching your back.
Hiding behind it from one like it?
Why'd you even come if you're so scared?
Scared?
Don't be ridiculous.
I always laugh at the face of danger.
Luffy!
Who's up?
Why'd you do that, you moron?
I didn't recognize you at first.
I thought you were more of Big
Mouse guards coming to fight.
Wow, I'm really surprised you
guys came all the way up here.
Well, not you, Zoro, but you, Usopp.
Aren't you normally scared of doing
stuff like climbing mountains?
Whenever there's a towering peak
in front of me, I get to climbing.
But let me tell you, scaling that
mountain hand over hand was no picnic!
Actually, we took a
ropeway car up here, Luffy.
Nami and Sanji, are they all right? Yeah!
Both of them are just fine!
I just have to say, we took a
ropeway car, but let me tell you,
taking it was no picnic!
Here's why.
We were on the way, then a giant condor
flew out of nowhere and attacked us.
So, what was that you were doing on
top of the castle a few minutes ago?
Beating the crap out of the king.
Oh. Okay.
You mean that person I saw flying
through the air was actually Wapol?
You beat him?
Yep, I sure did.
I threw a rope around his neck
and showed that bird who was boss.
Me, Captain Step!
And his two henchmen,
what happened to them?
Oh, well, the reindeer beat them up.
What? Those two? A reindeer?
Once again, Captain Usopp!
Oh, hey, Usopp!
I made a new friend!
And you gotta meet him!
Get this!
He's a reindeer!
Reindeer?
A reindeer...
It is you...
STOP!
I apologize for those who had the
nerve to laugh at Heraluk's death.
Without enough strength,
you'd only die in vain.
Don't waste your life.
Don't sacrifice it for this country.
Blue Nose, you never gave up, did you?
You still kept fighting, believing
in what this country could become.
And now, thanks to you, Drum
Kingdom, it can finally be reborn.
What?
What is that strange
creature behind that tree?
It almost looks like a reindeer.
No, you're wrong.
It's a monster.
No, don't shoot him!
It's a Yeti! No!
Somebody shoot him!
Jerk face!
He's not a Yeti, you idiot!
He's my new friend!
That thing's your friend?
You guys scared him so bad, he ran away!
I'll bring him back so you
can meet him, you jerks!
Hey!
Come back reindeer, I want to
introduce you to my friends!
I'm going to stop running for a second!
But my friends wouldn't meet you!
You wouldn't shoot me!
That's just because I don't know you yet!
Hey, slow down!
Where are you going?
My friends are back that way,
don't you want to meet us?
Doctor, this is for the best, isn't it?
They're not so bad, you'll see!
Come back and meet them,
they're my friends!
My friends like yours,
I don't need anything!
Are you sure you're
going to be okay, Dalton?
Yes, I'm fine.
Just feeling a little drained, that's all.
Hey!
You over there!
Dr. Kureha!
Yeah, it's good to see you too.
Now be useful and take the
injured guy to the medical ward.
Nami, you really should stay and
have your illness completely treated.
Be quiet.
If I don't escape from here now, we won't
be able to set sail for two more days.
You know how worried Vivi is.
We need to get her to Alabax.
Quit all this grumbling and
get back to the medical ward.
Move it!
Right now!
Just as I expected, his injuries have
gotten worse due to overexertion.
Much better.
Dalton, surely you would know
where the key to the arsenal is.
Isn't that right?
The arsenal?
Why do you need to get in there?
That's really none of
your business, now, is it?
Wapol always carried that key with
him to keep it secure, he said.
In which case, the key was likely
blown into the sky with him Oh, really?
Is that so?
Well, that's a shame Dr.
Ean
Think we can talk about your
fee for treating our crew?
Could you waive it?
Oh, and could you go ahead and
discharge me right now as well?
Is that a joke?
Because you should know better
than that by now, girly?
For my medical fee,
I will be taking all of the cargo and
money you have on that ship of yours!
And you will stay here and
recover for two more days.
Nami, she's right, you know.
You need to complete your treatment.
I'm fine.
I don't even feel like
I'm going to die anymore.
That isn't exactly a
very convincing reason.
The key to the arsenal.
This is what you needed, yeah?
How did you end up with that key?
If that's truly the real one,
how'd you get a hold of it?
I stole it.
You've certainly got some guts trying
to negotiate with me like this.
You really are an unbelievably
frustrating little girl, you know.
Okay, then.
You don't have to pay my doctor's fee,
but that's as much as I'll agree to.
As a doctor, I can't allow you
to leave in good conscience.
Not for two days.
Wait a second.
In that case, I'm afraid
we don't have a deal.
Give it back.
Listen here, girl.
I have to leave you alone now
and go take care of a few things.
If you look in the back room, you might
find a dresser with one of my coats in it.
And it's not exactly like I'm
posting any guards on you.
Also, the young man with the spinal fissure
should be well enough to travel by now.
But, girl, don't you even
think about trying to escape.
You guys, come with me.
I have some heavy lifting for you to do.
Okay, all right.
Did she really just tell us to steal
her coat, get Sanji, and sneak out?
I think so.
That's what it sounded like to me.
I sure have been running a long time.
Night came before I realized it.
I don't hear that rubber guy anymore.
Looks like I finally shook him, I guess.
This is for the best.
I can't leave this place.
I just can't.
Looks like a full moon tonight.
Hey, dear!
I can't believe it.
Those guys are still looking for me?
Come on, Luffy.
Why don't you just give it up?
We've been tracking him forever,
and he still hasn't shown up.
He's not interested in becoming a pirate.
You're just going to have to accept that.
No, that's not true.
I want the reindeer to
be a pirate with us.
Just because you want something
doesn't mean it's going to happen.
It's not that I don't
want to go with them.
Reindeer!
Wherever you are, reindeer, come out!
But I'm not going to go.
I can't go.
I'm nothing like them, the humans.
Reindeer guy!
Tony?
Hey, you're gonna come on our
ship and be a pirate with us, kay?
I can't.
Sure you can't, reindeer.
It's a whole lot of fun.
That's not a very good argument.
I can't.
I'm not a human, I'm a reindeer!
I have antlers and hooves, don't you see?
I even have a blue nose!
Now that you've heard his story, do you
think you can heal the scar on his heart?
Okay, maybe I do want to be a pirate!
But I can't ever be one of you!
I'm not human! I'm a monster!
I can't be your friend and I can't
become a pirate on your ship!
You see?
I'm just here to say...
thank you.
I appreciate you asking
me to join your ship.
That was really nice, so thank you.
I'm going to stay here for now.
But if you wanted to, you could
stop by here again. Shut up!
Let's go! No!
Most people don't make friends
by telling someone to shut up.
My life has been too still.
My heart is unfulfilled.
But you could be the one to set me free.
Something has to change.
My world can be rearranged.
I'll do anything as
long as you are with me.
I've grown stronger having you by my side.
We've started on an everlasting ride.
I'm invincible when your love is near.
When I'm with you I have no fear.
Let's see how far we can make this go.
The world is ours.
You're just right, I know.
I see it shine in the distance.
Glistening like water when
the sun Rises in the dawn.